Streib, Victor; Papers apap330
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1947-2012, Undated; 1; 19 cubic ft.
  - Sentenced Women, United States, 1983-2012, Undated; 1.2; 4 cubic ft.
    - Louisiana: Catherine Dodds, sentenced 1975, rev. 1976, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Louisiana: Antoinette Frank, sentenced 1995-09-14, 1994; 2006; 2008 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Louisiana: Brandy Holmes, sentenced 2006-02-21, 2009 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Maryland: Doris Foster, sentenced 1982-02-08, rev. 1987, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Maryland: Annette Stebbings, sentenced 1983-08-20, rev. 1985-12-20, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Mississippi: Susie Ann Balfur, sentenced 1989-10-14, rev. 1992-03-25 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Mississippi: Vernice Ballenger, sentenced 1993-01-13, 2002; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Mississippi: Sabrina Butler, sentenced 1990-06, rev. 1992-08-26 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Mississippi: Michelle Byrom, sentenced 2000-11-18, 2003; 2005 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Mississippi: Attina Connaday, sentenced 1982-09-21, rev. 1984, 1991 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Mississippi: Lisa Chamberlain, sentenced 2006-08-05, 2008 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Mississippi: Kristi Fulgham, sentenced 2006-12-09, 2007 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Mississippi: Carrie McCarthy, sentenced 1920, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Mississippi: Judy Houston, sentenced 1985-11-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Mississippi: Cecilia Williamson, sentenced 1984-03-14, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Missouri: Faye Copeland, sentenced 1991-04-27, rev. 1999-08-09, par. 2002-08-30, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Missouri: Sadie Hayes, sentenced 1885-01-15, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Missouri: Maria Isa, sentenced 1991-01-31 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Missouri: Shirley Jo Phillips, sentenced 1992-04-06, rev. 1997-02-25, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Missouri: Virginia Twenter, sentenced 1989-10-16, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Missouri: Nila Wacaser, sentenced 1988-05-31, died 1992-05-09, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Nevada: Pricilla Ford, sentenced 1982-04-29, died 2005-01-29, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Nevada: Sheila Summers, sentenced 1983-12-20, rev. 1986-12-20, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - New Jersey: Marie Moore, sentenced 1984-11-19, rev. 1988-10-26, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - New Jersey: Leslie Nelson, sentenced 1997-05 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - North Carolina: General, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - North Carolina: Melanie Anderson, sentenced 1996-09-26, 2003; 2008 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - North Carolina: Margie Baykin, sentenced 1975-12-10, rev. 1977-03-31, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - North Carolina: Faye Brown, sentenced 1976-01-17, rev. 1977-06-30, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - North Carolina: Sue Cox, sentenced 1987-11-02, rev. 1992-09-25, 1989; 2008; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - North Carolina: Rebecca Delter, sentenced 1978-09-26, rev. 1979, 2008; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - North Carolina: Yvette Gay, sentenced 1991-08-10, rev. 1993, 2008 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - North Carolina: Marie Hill, sentenced 1971, 2008 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - North Carolina: Rozell Oxendine Hunt, sentenced 1974-06-13, rev. 1976-12-15, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - North Carolina: Patrica Jennings, sentenced 1990-11-05, 2003; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - North Carolina: Christine Kemmerlin, sentenced 2000-10-17, rev. 2002-12-20, 2003; 2008 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - North Carolina: Marilyn Mahaley, sentenced 1990-12-17, rev. 1994, 2008; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - North Carolina: Blanche Moore, sentenced 1990-11-16, 1999; 2007; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - North Carolina: Carlette Parker, sentenced 1999-04-01, 2003; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - North Carolina: Barbara Stager, sentenced 1989-05-19, rev. 1991-08-14, 2008; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - North Carolina: Christina Walters, sentenced 2000-07-06, 2003; 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - North Carolina: Mamie Lee Ward, sentenced 1973-09-19, rev. 1976-09-01, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Ohio: Debra Brown, sentenced 1985-06-18, rev. 1991-01-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Ohio: Nicole Diar, sentenced 2005-11-02, 2008 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Ohio: Rosalie Grant, sentenced 1983-10-21, 1990; 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Ohio: Elizabeth Green, sentenced 1988-07-11, rev. 1991-01-10, 1989; 2005; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Ohio: Beatrice Lampkin, sentenced 1989-04-26, rev. 1991-01-10, 2005; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Ohio: Sandra Lockett, sentenced 1977, rev. 1978, rel. 1993, 1991; 1994; 1997; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Ohio: Alberta Osbourne, sentenced 1975-06-02, rev. 1991-01-10, 1990 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Ohio: Donna Roberts, sentenced 2003-06-21, 2004 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Ohio: Donna Roberts, sentenced 2003-06-21, News Reports (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Ohio: Donna Roberts, Merit Brief Plaintiff - Apellee of State of Ohio, 2004 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Ohio: Donna Roberts, Merit Brief of Apellant, Donna Roberts, 2004 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Ohio: Beuita Smith, sentenced 1977, rev. 1970-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Ohio: Patrica Wernet, sentenced 1976-11-22, rev. 1978, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Ohio: Sharon Young, sentenced 1983-09-30, 1993; 1997; 2003; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Oklahoma: Brenda Andrew, sentenced 2004-09-23, 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Oklahoma: Michelle Binsz, sentenced 1979-10-23, rev. 1984-03-01, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Oklahoma: Patrica Jones, sentenced 1989-12-07, 1990; 1993; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Oklahoma: Janet Miller, sentenced 1975-08-26, rev. 1976-01-12, rel. 1983-09-12, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Oklahoma: Delpha Spunaugle, sentenced 1995-03-31, 2005 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Oregon: Jeannaie Freeman, sentenced 1961, rev. 1964, rel. 1980's, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Oregon: Angela McAnulty, sentenced 2011-02-25 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Pennsylvania: Donetta Hill, sentenced 1992-04-09, 1998; 2004; 2006 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania: Carolyn King, sentenced 1994-11-30, rev. 2010-08-06, 1995; 1999; 2003; 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania: Beth Ann Markman, sentenced 2001, 2002 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania: Kelly O'Donnell, sentenced 1993-07-01, 2002; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania: Delores Rivers, sentenced 1989-03-16, rev. 2005-05, 1993; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania: Michelle Tharp, sentenced 2000-11, 2001; 2003 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania: Shonda Walter, sentenced 2005-04-19 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - South Carolina: Rebecca Smith, sentenced 1990-12-11, 1991; 1994; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Tennessee: Gail Owens, sentenced 1986-01-15, rev. 2010, par. 2011, 2005 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Tennessee: Christa Gail Pike, sentenced 1996-03-29, 2001; 2003; 2005; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Texas: General, 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Texas: Mary Lou Anderson, sentenced 1978-08-29, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Texas: Susan Basso, sentenced 1999-09-01, 2002; 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Texas: Kenisha Berry, sentenced 2004-02-19, rev. 2007-05, 2008 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Texas: Linda May Burnett, sentenced 1979-03-20, rev. 1983, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Texas: Linda Carty, sentenced 2002-02-21, 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Texas: Lisa Coleman, sentenced 2006-07-07, 2007; 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Texas: Cathy Henderson, sentenced 1995-05-30, 2002; 2007; 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Texas: Cathy Henderson, sentenced 1995-05-30, News Report, 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Texas: Cathy Henderson, sentenced 1995-05-30, Trial Documents, 2007 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Texas: Brittany Holberg, sentenced 1998-03-27, 1999; 2002; 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Texas: Melissa Lucio, sentenced 2008-08-12, 2009; 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Texas: Kimberly McCarthy, sentenced 1998-11-24, [ex. 2013-06-26, 2001; 2012; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Texas: Pamela Perillo, sentenced 1984-11-13, rev. 2000-07, 1996; 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Texas: Chelsea Richardson, sentenced 2005-06-01, rev. 2011-01-17, 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Texas: Darlie Router, sentenced 1997-02-04, 2005; 2012 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Texas: Erica Sheppard, sentenced 1995-03-03, 1999; 2002; 2012; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Virginia: General - Lesbians, 1997; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Florida: Andrea Jackson, Emergency Motion to Vacate Judgement, 1989 April 5 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Florida: Andrea Jackson, Appendix to Emergency Motion to Vacate Judgement, Vol. 1, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Florida: Andrea Jackson, Appendix to Emergency Motion to Vacate Judgement, Vol. 2.1, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Florida: Andrea Jackson, Appendix to Emergency Motion to Vacate Judgement, Vol. 2.2, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Florida: Andrea Jackson, Appendix to Emergency Motion to Vacate Judgement, Vol. 3.1, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Florida: Andrea Jackson, Appendix to Emergency Motion to Vacate Judgement, Vol. 3.1, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Executed Juveniles, United States, 1982-2007, Undated; 1.3; 4 cubic ft.
    - Alabama: General, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Alabama: Robert Alexander, executed 1893-05-26, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Alabama: (Alfred) Godfrey, executed 1858-07-16, 1985; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Alabama: Brad (Bud) Beard, executed 1897-12-17, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Alabama: Bob Brown, executed 1902-01-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Alabama: Lucius Carter, executed 1917-11-09, 2007 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Alabama: William Clark, executed 1941-01-17, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Alabama: Henry Gardner, executed 1899-09-15, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Alabama: Henry, executed 1866-04-20, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Alabama: Beauty Ingram, executed 1900-05-18, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Alabama: Melvin Jackson, executed 1956-09-28, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Alabama: Ernest Johnson, executed 1946-01-25, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Alabama: Issac Johnson, executed 1869-03-12, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Alabama: Joe Henry Johnson, executed 1961-11-24, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Alabama: John Johnson, executed 1891-01-16, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Alabama: Larkin (Bibb), executed 1858-09-27, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Alabama: Sam Mawll, executed 1892-07-08, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Alabama: Frank Millhouse, executed 1938-01-28, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Alabama: Nathan Moseley, executed 1886-10-08, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Alabama: Howard Pugh, executed 1893-05-26, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Alabama: Louis Pugh, executed 1893-05-26, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Alabama: Jeremiah Reeves, executed 1958-03-28, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Alabama: Willie James Whitfield, executed 1938-08-19, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Arizona: General, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Arizona: Demetrio Dominguez, executed 1880-11-26, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Arizona: Manuel Hernandez, executed 1934-07-06, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Arkansas: General, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Arkansas: Fred Arnell, executed 1939-05-19, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Arkansas: John Billy, executed 1874-04-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Arkansas: Henry Burnett, executed 1885-08-26, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Arkansas: Omer Davis, executed 1913-09-11, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Arkansas: Lonnie Dixon, executed 1927-06-24, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Arkansas: Jay Greene, executed 1903-03-20, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Arkansas: Silas Hampton, executed 1887-10-07, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Arkansas: Joseph Kemp, executed 1879-10-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Arkansas: Harry Poe, executed 1910-09-02, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Arkansas: John Pointer, executed 1874-04-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Arkansas: James Wells, es. 1922-03-10, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - California: General, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - California: Augustine Louis, executed 1911-01-20, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - California: Henry Brown, executed 1906-09-07, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - California: Lawrence C. Campbell, executed 1923-06-22, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - California: Louis Dabner, executed 1908-07-31, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - California: Charles E.T. Oxnam, executed 1916-03-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - California: Yuki Indian, executed 1864-12-07, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Connecticut: General, 1982; 1986; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Connecticut: Charles B. Cross, executed 1900-07-20, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Connecticut: Michael Jennings, executed 1854-07-11, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Connecticut: Hannah Ocuish, executed 1786-12-20, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Delaware: John Green, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Delaware: Frederick Young, executed 1891-02-13, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Federal: General, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Federa;" James Arcene, executed 1885-06-26, 1985; 1999; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Federal: George Crab, Thomas Ferry, James Lysaught and James Knight, executed 1866-01-26, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Federal: David Owen Dodd, executed 1864-01-08, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Federal: Issac Fillmore, executed 1874-04-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Federal: Paddy Mullins, executed 1864-04-23, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Federal: Abraham Purvis, executed 1865-01-13, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Federal: Sinker Wilson, executed 1876-09-08, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Federal: Amy Spain, executed 1865-03-10, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Florida: Abraham Beard, executed 1954-11-08, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Florida: Willie B. Clay, executed 1941-12-29, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Florida: James Davis, executed 1944-10-09, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Florida: Fortune Ferguson, executed 1927-04-27, 1984; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Florida: Irving Hanchett, executed 1910-05-06, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Florida: Monroe Hasty, executed 1935-09-16, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Florida: Robert Hinds, executed 1937-07-23, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Florida: Orion Johnson, executed 1954-09-28, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Florida: Freddie Lee Lane, executed 1944-10-09, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Florida: Edward Powell, executed 1941-12-29, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Florida: Guilford Register, executed 1867-04-19, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Florida: Ernest James "Smokey" Robinson, executed 1942-08-17, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Florida: Lacy Stewart, executed 1948-10-25, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Florida: Nathaniel Walker, executed 1941-12-29, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Florida: Ivory Lee Williams, executed 1940-11-11, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Georgia: General, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Georgia: Lee James Allen, executed 1946-11-15, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Georgia: Charlie Anderson, executed 1941-05-23, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Georgia: Isiah Ashley, executed 1935-04-05, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Georgia: Reuben Battle, executed 1898-12-16, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Georgia: Willie Bell, executed 1892-11-29, 1982; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Georgia: Eddie B. Bowen, executed 1936-03-06, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Georgia: Edward Brooks, executed 1895-05-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Georgia: Leonard Brown, executed 1937-05-24, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Georgia: Boisey Bryant, executed 1902-09-12, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Georgia: Christopher A. Burger, executed 1993-12-07, 1986; 1990; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Georgia: Bartow Cantrell, executed 1914-07-31, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Georgia: Ed Capers, executed 1929-01-18, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Georgia: Don Mitchell Coleman, executed 1957-03-19, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Georgia: Charles Dodson, executed 1935-01-21, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Georgia: Bernice Franklin, executed 1943-05-28, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Georgia: King Crosby, executed 1900-04-06, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Georgia: Lewis Goosby, executed 1900-04-06, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Georgia: Tricey Griffin, executed 1901-06-14, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Georgia: Margaret Harris, executed 1883-10-19, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Georgia: Sam Harris, executed 1900-01-05, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Georgia: Willie Hicks, executed 1944-02-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Georgia: Buck High, executed 1907-05-29, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Georgia: Jose' High, executed 2001-11-06, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Georgia: Jose' High, executed 2001-11-06, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Georgia: J.C. Hill, executed 1946-12-20, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Georgia: Willie Jackson, Jr. and Herman Lee Miller, executed 1954-06-15, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Georgia: John Albert and Wilbur Gene Jones, executed 1949-09-12, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Georgia: Joe Lee Jones, executed 1954-11-19, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Georgia: Charles King, executed 1954-11-19, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Georgia: Robert Kitchens, executed 1916-06-02, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Georgia: Little William (Stiles), executed 1829-07-24, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Georgia: James Magnum, executed 1948-03-05, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Georgia: James W. Morgan, executed 1955-01-07, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Georgia: Richard Morris Richard Sims, and Mose White, executed 1933-08-11, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Georgia: Negro Man, executed 1848-08-28, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Georgia: Reuben O' Neal, executed 1892, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Georgia: Will Osborne, executed 1934-01-12, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Georgia: homer Perry, executed 1884-11-08, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Georgia: Joe Persons, executed 1915-09-24, 2007; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Georgia: Herbert Lee Reddick, executed 1947-06-30, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Georgia: Charlie Rucker, executed 1938-12-09, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Georgia: Ed Sally, executed 1876-04-29, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Georgia: Charlie "Jewboy" Sexton, executed 1943-08-20, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Georgia: Wash Smith, executed 1930-11-22, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Georgia: Willie Stevenson, executed 1946-11-22, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Georgia: Harris Sutton, executed 1917-01-12, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Georgia: Jack Thomasson, executed 1877-07-06, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Georgia: James Thompson, executed 1858-07-02, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Georgia: David Watkins, executed 1945-05-11, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Georgia: Ambrose West, executed 1883-11-30, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Georgia: Jesse Williams, executed 1882-01-16, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Georgia: Pringle Williams, executed 1926-10-08, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Indiana: James Swain, executed 1939-06-23, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Indiana: John Anderson, executed 1884-01-25, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Indiana: William Ray, executed 1920-04-28, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Iowa: General, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Iowa: James Dooley, executed 1894-10-09, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Illinois: Anthony Grecco and Charles Waltz, executed 1929-02-20, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Kentucky: General, 1994-05-27, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Kentucky: Bill (James), executed 1791-07-30, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Kentucky: James Buckner, executed 1911-07-08, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Kentucky: Eugene Burnam, executed 1942-03-27, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Kentucky: Robert Charlton, executed 1890-11-27, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Kentucky: Robert Cheney, executed 1879-05-16, 1995; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Kentucky: Carl Fox, executed 1945-04-06, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)